so no and you shouldn't really strive
for that because you have to understand
how a negative Loop Works which is what
our endocrine system is designed to do
specifically the hypothalamic pituitary
testicular axis it's a negative feedback
which means that when one signal goes up
it drives another signal and then when
that signal goes up the initial
signaling agent drops so when
luteinizing hormone levels go up and you
produce more testosterone that
testosterone production causes that LH
level to drop when you introduce
exogenous levels of testosterone that
are sufficient for your body your
luteinizing hormone levels will be
suppressed they will drop so the short
answer is no the longer answer is we can
mimic luteinizing hormone with
luteinizing hormone analoges such as HCG
so a little bit of HCG
drizzled usually about twice a week on a
low dose can maintain testicular
function we use it in patients who want
to prevent testicular atrophy and only
about 25% of patients actually do
experience it so it's not a one- siiz
fits all and we use it in patients who
may want to conceive a child in the
future again to maintain the latex cell
activity within their testicles so in
the future when they are ready to
conceive we can add in a medication
called FSH or follicle stimulating
hormone which helps the production of
sperm also called
spermatogenesis so all of this could be
done if we want to preserve some level
of testicular function uh but when it
comes to actual hormone regulation it's
not needed your exogenous testosterone
when managed correctly is more than
sufficient to give you everything you'll
need
[Music]